<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogchain - A Blockchain Blog</title><link>http://blogchain.wtf/</link><description>Recent content on Blogchain - A Blockchain Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 09:55:29 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://blogchain.wtf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>http://blogchain.wtf/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://blogchain.wtf/about/</guid><description>A Little About Me Blogchain is a personal blogspace written and maintained by Kiran Hegde. I&amp;rsquo;m Information Science and Engineering student at RV College of Engineering, Bengaluru. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently developed a keen interest about blockchain and love open source projects. I&amp;rsquo;m open for collaboration with any projects in the space. Feel free to ping me on any platform.</description></item><item><title>Flash Loans, Flashier Attacks !</title><link>http://blogchain.wtf/post/flash-loans-flashier-attacks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 09:55:29 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://blogchain.wtf/post/flash-loans-flashier-attacks/</guid><description>Most of the content in this post is either from or inspired by this paper. If you would rather read it, go ahead and skip this post.
Decentralized Finance. Decentralized Finance is an effort to bring the benefits of distributed ledger technologies to the real world of finance. Instead of the financial institution knowing their customers to ensure their trust is well placed, you are able to transparently view all of the Smart Contracts, security practices, security audits to effectively Know Your Bank.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started With Ethereum</title><link>http://blogchain.wtf/post/getting-started-with-ethereum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:02:37 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://blogchain.wtf/post/getting-started-with-ethereum/</guid><description>With Ethereum 2.0 underway, There is not a better time to jump into the interesting world of Blockchain. As a Hello World ! program, Let&amp;rsquo;s create a smart contract and walk through its working.
What is Ethereum ? Ethereum was conceptually started by Vitalik Buterin, When he was trying to curb the problems of existing cryptocurrencies. As he states (In this post), his goal was to make Ethereum a platform for building digital money and creating smart autonomous programs that could efficiently handle digital assets.</description></item></channel></rss>